aroundyou.com.au 2013-06-20

# Privacy

* * *

The AroundYou privacy policy governs the use of information that may be collected from you when you visit the AroundYou website. The AroundYou privacy policy forms part of our commitment to the Privacy Act 1988 (Cth).

This policy tells you how we use personal information collected at the AroundYou website. Please read this privacy policy before using this website or submitting any personal information either directly or indirectly. By using the website, you are accepting the practices described in this privacy policy. AroundYou may change these practices at any time but such changes will only apply to activities and information on a going forward, not a retroactive basis. You are encouraged to review the privacy policy whenever you visit the website to make sure that you understand how any personal information you provide will be used.

**Note:** the privacy practices set forth in this privacy policy are for the AroundYou website only. If you link to other websites, please review the privacy policies posted at those sites.

#### Collection of Information

AroundYou may collect personally identifiable information, like names, email addresses etc., when voluntarily submitted by visitors to the AroundYou website. The information you provide is used to fulfil your specific request, in addition to adding you to our mailing list unless you specifically request removal from such a list. AroundYou has the right to use the information you provide to assist it in growing its business and to use such information to encourage other users to visit and use the website.

#### Cookie/Tracking Technology

When visiting the website, a record of your visit is logged and such record may be used to assist AroundYou in enhancing your future search activities during subsequent visits to the website. The website may use cookie and tracking technology depending on the features offered. Cookie and tracking technology are useful for gathering information such as browser type and operating system, tracking the number of visitors to the website and understanding how visitors use the site. Cookies can also help customise the website for our visitors and helps us identify you as an individual.

Personal information is not collected by cookies or other tracking technology; however, if you previously provided personally identifiable information, cookies may be tied to such information. Aggregate cookie and tracking information may be shared with third parties. Most browsers are set up to accept cookies to enhance a users experience with the website, but if your browser permits it, you can elect to have your browser reject cookies which includes cookies affiliated with the AroundYou website.

#### Distribution of Information

We may share information with government agencies or other companies assisting us in fraud prevention, minimising inappropriate behaviour over the internet or such other relevant investigation or reporting deemed appropriate by AroundYou, or if required by law or regulation for some other enforceable purpose. In addition to providing this information if required by law or regulation, we may also provide it when trying to protect against or to prevent actual or potential fraud or unauthorised or inappropriate activities or when investigating fraud or such related matter that has already taken place. The information is not provided to any government agencies or fraud prevention/investigation companies for marketing purposes.

If AroundYou believes you are submitting information that a reasonable person considers to be inappropriate for the wide audience of AroundYou website users, AroundYou reserves the right to forward your details to the appropriate authority that is considered to have statutory, regulatory or voluntary stewardship of the governance practices of on-line content as it pertains to the broad activities of AroundYou.

#### Commitment to Data Security

Your personally identifiable information is kept secure to the extent that all reasonable efforts are made to prevent unauthorised access to our store of data. Only authorised employees, agents and contractors (who have agreed to keep information secure and confidential) have access to this information. AroundYou does not keep any details of your credit card or banking information even if you use the AroundYou website to link with other websites that require such information for booking or purchase purposes.

AroundYou does not provide for the secure transmission of information across the internet. Users should be aware that there are risks associated with transmitting information across the internet and any information they provide or share with any individual or organisation could be used for purposes other than for which such sharing was originally intended.

#### Privacy Contact Information

If you have any questions, concerns or comments about this privacy policy you may contact AroundYou using the information below.

**By email** [info@aroundyou.com.au](mailto:info@aroundyou.com.au)
